<?xml version="1.0"?>
<evemon xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <newest>
    <date>22 May 2011</date>
    <version>1.4.0.2761</version>
    <url>http://forum.battleclinic.com/index.php/topic,144054.0.html</url>
    <autopatchurl>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/installers/EVEMon-install-1.4.0.2761.exe</autopatchurl>
    <autopatchargs>/S /AUTORUN /SKIPDOTNET</autopatchargs>
    <additionalargs>/D=%EVEMON_EXECUTABLE_PATH%</additionalargs>
    <message><![CDATA[== Breaking Changes ==

* EVEMon Relocator has been deprecated (removed).
* Non-Public skills will not show correct info as CCP removed the related info from their database.


== Contributors for this version ==

* Jimi
* Richard Slater
* ykoehler


== New Features ==

* EVEMon now shows the status of an account and notifies the user when subscription is close to expiration.
* EVEMon now has a Blank Character Creator.
* EVEMon now has an EVE Mail Messages monitor.
* EVEMon now has an EVE Notifications monitor.
* EVEMon has now the ability to store the settings file to the BattleClinic server via the BattleClinic API service.


== Bugfixes ==

* EVEMon will no longer crash when right clicking on an unknown skill in queue.
* EVEMon will not send any notifications for non monitored characters or non monitored full api key features.
* EVEMon can now query both EVE Servers (Tranquility and Sinqularity) (use with caution and at your own risk as switching to Sinqularity and opening the Skill Planner will affect your plans).
* EVEMon now sees the correct path of the default cached EVE portrait folder.
* EVEMon will no longer crash on Implant Calc when any non in-game implant is selected in an implant set.
* Fixes a minor visual bug in Research monitor.
* Fixes a minor visual bug in Industry jobs monitor.
* Fixes a minor visual bug in Market orders monitor.
* Reordered columns in research points monitor will now be remembered.
* Fixes a bug when plan ends exactly at the end of the page, only the next page gets printed.
* Fixes a bug where the IGB connection was left open (if in use) when EVEMon restarts after a data file update.
* Fixes an issue where the port of the IGB server was not validated.
* Fixes the sorting issue for the plan column "Group". Notice that the sorting criterion is the duration of each group and not the name. 
* Fixes a visual bug for the dropdown menu of "Plan To..." in Skill browser.
* Fixes a visual bug in Skill browser where upon right clicking a fully level trained skill, "Plan To..." is enabled.


== Enhancements ==

* New enhanced installer.
* Overview now shows the total training time of the skill queue.
* Default character picture (no avatar) has been updated to the post Incursion one.
* EVEMon planner now has another column showing the skill points required for each skill level.
* Character info now shows birthday, ancestry and upon hovering over the corporation name, the alliance the corp is a member of.
* EVE icons now have the Tech or Metagroup overlay icon.
* All monitored characters query timers can now be updated manually (via Tools>Options>General>Updates).
* EVEMon windows will no longer open on top of each other.
* Improved visualization of each monitor.
* Level 0 known skills added in tooltip info of a character's known skills.
* CCP icons will now be fetched from CCP's Image Server.
* Order of compared items in browser will now be by selection.
* Corp related monitoring get disabled if character is in NPC corporation.
* Activity description has been added next to the blueprint enabled by each skill level in Skill Explorer.
* A "Research" tab has been added to the Blueprint browser for those blueprints that don't have any research prerequisites (invention excluded) in order to be able to switch between research facilities (laboratories).
* EVEMon now handles more gracefully CCP error notifications when EVE Backend Database is temporarily disabled (no more endless notifications list, only one notification is now shown).


== Misc ==

* "<None>" implant indicator renamed to "None".]]></message>
  </newest>
  <datafiles>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-blueprints-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>19 May 2011</date>
      <md5>197b86c16ab1b49090eb351c843d4a40</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incursion/259851</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incursion 1.5.0 (259851) blueprints data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-certificates-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>19 May 2011</date>
      <md5>0e0beef2a7d3d8196d42b587babb3e35</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incursion/259851</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incursion 1.5.0 (259851) certificates data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-geography-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>19 May 2011</date>
      <md5>f4c478a217db35209cfe3c3ed79990b7</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incursion/259851</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incursion 1.5.0 (259851) geography data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-items-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>19 May 2011</date>
      <md5>5360dba7008511c0530c9d5d11db8cfb</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incursion/259851</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incursion 1.5.0 (259851) items data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-properties-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>19 May 2011</date>
      <md5>dd93ef5db2cb1d112c9fd471ff47fe5d</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incursion/259851</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incursion 1.5.0 (259851) properties data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-reprocessing-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>19 May 2011</date>
      <md5>322a64607ae565e7d0af03ea9bfc9783</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incursion/259851</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incursion 1.5.0 (259851) reprocessing data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-skills-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>19 May 2011</date>
      <md5>5873fe248ac8e3f4436cf789ccdb7773</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incursion/259851</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incursion 1.5.0 (259851) skills data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
  </datafiles>
</evemon>